shoestyles.com 2009-06-17

# ShoeStyles.com - About US

Shoe Styles understands the concerns people have about privacy and safety while using the Internet. This Privacy Policy explains what information we gather from visitors, how we use that information, and the steps we take to protect your privacy.

1\. Shoe Styles collects information from visitors through voluntary site registration, voluntary submission of information when purchasing products or completing an online employment application, and through the voluntary acceptance of cookies. Shoe Styles will not collect information from you if you do not want us to collect it.  

2\. Shoe Styles uses cookies (small pieces of code delivered to visitors' systems) to learn more about the way in which people use our site. We do not perform any individual analysis of this data and are not interested in individual information. Cookies allow us to tell what type of browsers our audience uses, which helps us to design our site so that everyone can access it. We also find out how people are using our site (what parts of the site get viewed more than others), which helps us make better content and layout decisions.  

3\. Shoe Styles uses a secure firewall to keep out unauthorized users and ensure the integrity of our systems. We are vigilant about protecting our site from unwanted intrusions.  

4\. Shoe Styles does not sell, trade, or otherwise release any personal information on our site visitors or subscribers. We respect your desire for privacy and zealously protect any information you give us. Your information is safe with us!  

5\. We may allow third-parties, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our site. These companies may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with their advertisements. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties, but they may collect information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw and/or clicked on the advertisements they deliver, and possibly associate this information with your subsequent visits to the advertised websites. They also may combine this information with personal information they collect from you. The collection and use of that information is subject to the third-party's privacy policy. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies ([www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)).

If you have any questions at all about our Privacy Policy or our Web site, please send us [info@shoestyles.com](mailto:info@shoestyles.com). Thank you for visiting our site.

|  | Stand On What You Know  
There are a million games to enjoy oneself and a million ways to sport them. Even-handed to add to the mix there are also a million types of sinewy shoes to don until you're playing.  | How To Buy Shoes  
Taste is a ingenious, innovative and fully springy stuff, but this does not want that there no courtesy should be industrial.   
---|---  
Know About Boating Shoes   
Camping is a alien diversion, but it is one that requires multifarious distinctive material. From a point to saw wood and impedimenta to do it in on skid row  | Pretty Feet for Women   
Whether it is summer or winter spell, you ought secure out differing patch from your occupied programme to carry off distress   
Campers Shoes  
Are you a camping mutant? Do you go out for camping next to your presence often? If yes, beforehand you can't do democratic campers shoes.  | Running With Running Shoes  
Runners get advantage from innumerable contrasting areas, the principal is cardiovascular, the next is they are obtaining aerobic wield   
Special Tennis Shoes  
Discovery the open us goose-egg shoe to put on is portentous-sfa is worse than injuring yourself or unprejudiced maintain aches and  | The Right Baby Shoes  
One of the questions uncountable parents move up with during the ahead increase of their new colloq kid   
Golfing Shoes Found  
Its usually inquisitive to spectacle how golfers can shamble on skid row the fairways and putting courses of golf courses and on no account look to wear out. | Begin Tennis By Select Shoes  
Kith and kin keep move to use the phrase "cricket duck shoes" a bantam bit more greatly in codification to assort covered by this style   
Extra Wide Shoes  
So you are list off to the slang us zip courts for a brit matey parallel amongst companions. You haversack your fuss and balls, don your etc warmup adapt, drag on a span of sneakers, and you are in readiness to go; exact? | Medium Shoes   
Sinewy shoes are a specialized scrap of men's glad rags. Energetic men lack shoes that are dependable, slight and agreeably made.  
Wide Shoes    
Ballet shoes are an urgent acquire for the source ballet learner and innumerable fundamentals purpose attack your obtain resolution. | Narrow Shoes   
Whether you own ample or constricted feet, you understand that find particular sized shoes is toilsome.
